My enemy is near.
Give me the strength.
And my hand to kill him and return alive to kill those who remain.
May all evil omens, the dire cry of birds,
whom align conjunction of stars, all evil dreams and angry words.
Master?
The samurai is honorable.
You are no samurai.
May they all be drained of power.
The ninth level.
Feller.
95, 96, 97, 98, 99.
5, 96, 97, 98, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99
99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99, 99
Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh
Uh-uhMUSIC Uh-uh uh uh Reporter
I'm sorry.
S applause for me.
I was raised not singing about trees.
I was raised not listening to voice of cues.
playing.
Belarus.
Yield Kheikopiano.
A good sourness.
I never tire of your people's aversion to impoliteness, a taboo against a fence, even
as you've planned the death of thousands.
Surely not so many need to die.
Anyone who stands in the way, anyone not on their knees when it's over.
Your guns will be ready?
They are all ready, already ready, ready for all.
All we need are loyal men ready to fire them.
You ask Master Chiefa to wage a his excellent position as advisor to the Shogun.
The wrists are great.
Thousands of men guard the Shogun's castle.
Ten thousand.
Twenty, it doesn't matter.
They guard it with knives.
No one makes a better blade than your people.
No one invents better ways to kill people than mine.
A gun will never be as beautiful as a sword, but with a gun you can take any sword you
want.
The Shogun and his entire family will be dead, come spring.
And Master Chiba will be the right hand of our appointed man.
That was tasteless of me.
Our men are trained and eager to serve.
Each one hates the Shogun with all the blood in his heart.
Oh, I don't hate the Shogun.
I just want his chair.
It's him.
He's come.
I told you he'd come.
I want to watch.
Why set traps only to mash the rat yourself?
Sit.
We have business.
I want to watch.
But you know what's next.
My flowers.
It won't be enough.
Fine.
And you're a giant.
You'll get yourself killed.
Or a monster.
No one can know you're hiding.
I thought you had to be something special.
Go ahead.
Just jump.
Jump.
It felt dark.
Master.
Ringo.
Miso.
I can.
That.
That's my scarf.
Again.
Are you real?
I think so.
Can you walk?
It might be slow.
This is up.
Down.
Is that way?
We're not leaving.
We're going to the night level.
I have a man to kill.
I hate you.
Deep party.
Put me back in the dungeon.
I hate you.
I'm not afraid.
My whole life has been a battle.
An apprentice would never leave his master's side.
I'll avenge his mama.
I swear.
I hate you.
He's nowhere.
He disappeared.
I told you I said this Samurai could not be stopped.
But you wouldn't listen.
Just a man.
Let him come.
Perhaps we should excuse ourselves from their danger.
What danger?
An attack on the Shogun's emissaries and an attack on the Shogun himself.
No one would dare attack them with us here.
Yes.
That's true.
A blazerfaler.
Where is he?
Oh.
You see, no one murders so well as the British.
It's our number one export.
Look at you.
No one's ever made it up half this far before.
How did you like our monkeys?
Well, you found your friend.
He was stupidly loyal.
I mean, wouldn't tell us a thing about you.
Not even to save his fingernails.
You came all this way for me because of what I just made to you.
Maybe?
I thought I'd kinded for all my bastards over the years.
They lined the tunnel you came in.
All those half breeds like you.
I'll kill you.
All four of you.
I see.
It wasn't.
I heard something happened to Old Violet.
Was that you?
For Violet.
You still alive.
Why?
I know what I'm supposed to do.
Be a samurai.
Like you.
Okay.
I'll teach you.